

OBJECTIVE

To work in an inspiring environment surrounded by creative minds who connect well through great communication.

PROFILE

I am a Creative Design Specialist. I have been pursuing graphic design for about six years. My expertise spans more than just creating compelling designs. I also specialize in begining-to-end project managment to ensure the designs I create achieve the desired outcome of the project. I work to evolve ideas from concept to finished product.

EDUCATION

The School of Advertising Art, August 2012—May 2014 | Kettering, OH Associate Degree of Applied Business in Advertising Art

Terra Community College, August 2009—May 2012 | Fremont, OH PSEO General Education, Photography, Web Design, and Print Design

SKILLS

Proficient in the following:

- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign
- Some experience with HTML and CSS

Design experience includes:

- Visual identity sets, business cards, brand creation, and brand standards development
- Fliers, banners, signs, apparel design, stickers, and packaging
- Website and interactive media design

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Designer, 2010—Present Print, branding, and web design work

Journeys, October 2014—Present | Nashville, TN Junior Designer

Worked on mostly print items internally and in-store while collaborating with a team to make tight deadlines without letting the quality suffer.

Apparel, in-store signange, internal design, ads and more

U! Creative, April 2014—May 2014 | Dayton, OH Design Intern

Worked on various projects, for a wide variety of clients, doing mostly production work and helping out the team with whatever they needed.

ZACHHALFHILL.COM ZACHHALFHILL@GMAIL.COM 567-201-6910

Journeys, October 2012—2014 | Dayton, OH

Sales Associate

Dedicated service following Journeys' corporate approach, which focuses on creating a friendly environment for each customer.

4100 CENTRAL PIKE #303 HERMITAGE, TN 37076